ここはね
7,000万年前の地球だよ
まゆり？
オカリンは タイムマシンで
ここに送られちゃったんだ
This is Earth, seventy million years ago.
まゆりなのか？
まゆしぃはね
オカリンを追いかけて
Mayuri?
たくさん たくさん たっくさんの
世界線のオカリンを
You were sent here by a time machine.
捜し続けてきたのです
Is that you, Mayuri?
まゆり…
Mayushii has looked for Okarin
ここにいるオカリンも
たくさんいるオカリンの１人って
言えるし
in many, many, many world lines, chasing him.
オリジナルだっても言えるし
ここにいる まゆしぃも
Mayuri?
たくさんいる まゆしぃのうちの
１人っても言えるし
You could say that the Okarin here
is one of many Okarins.
And you could say that
オリジナルだっても言えるの
he's the original Okarin.
でね オカリンも まゆしぃも
ここで死んじゃうと思う
And you could also say the Mayushii here
is one of many Mayushiis.
And you could say that
でも きっと
7,000万年後の秋葉原にいる
オカリンと まゆしぃまで
she's the original, too.
And so,
意思は連続していくんだって思う
I think Okarin and Mayushii are gonna die here.
だから…
あっ！
大丈夫だよ
But I believe
that our wills will carry on
to the Okarin and Mayushii, in Akihabara,
seventy million years from now.
So...
It's okay.
オカリ～ン！
Dogma in Ergosphere
あっ…
紅莉栖ちゃんが そろそろ
完成するから来てくれって！
あとね まゆしぃのコスもね…
Okarin!
うん？
さあ！ 早く 早く！
Kurisu-chan says to come in,
because she's almost done.
And Mayushii's cosplay...
Well...
Come on! Come on!
これをね 持っててくれないかなあ
Do you think you could hold this?
こうか？
そうそう！
Like this?
That's right. Keep it spread out like that!
そうやって
ビロ～ンって広げたままね
ウフッ…
へえ～ そのリボン かわいいわね
That ribbon's cute.
でしょ～？
あっ 紅莉栖ちゃんも着てみる？
Right?
Want to try it on?
今度のコミマ まだ コスあるよ
I still have some cosplay outfits for Comima.
コスプレか…
もしかして 興味あるん？
Cosplay, huh?
Interested?
そ そんなわけないでしょ！
こんなの 人前で着るなんて…
N-No way!
I couldn't wear this around others...
あっ…
出来た～！
うん？
It's done!
ジャ～ン！
私の勝ちだね 競争してたんだ
I win!
We were racing.
やられた
でも こっちも もう終わり
I lose.
But we're done, too.
これで 完成
うん？
Now we're done.
これが… タイムリープマシンよ
This is...
a time leap machine.
あっ…
へえ～
こうやって見ると
悪の組織の催眠メカみたいだお
It looks like an evil organization's
brainwashing machine.
う～ん 帽子付き電話レンジちゃん
みたいな感じだね
It's like Phone Microwave-chan,
now with headphones!
見てくれは
ちゃちかもしれないけど
It may not look like much,
理論上は これで 記憶を
過去に送ることができるはずよ
but theoretically, this can transmit
memories into the past.
ＬＨＣが使える今なら特にね
Especially now that we can use the LHC.
ＬＨＣが関係あるのか？
The LHC's involved?
ええ 簡単に言うと圧縮の問題
Yes, it's basically a problem of compression.
前も言ったように
Me on 2010/8/13 AD                    Hippocampus
Like I said,
この機械で 脳の中にある
記憶部分の信号を読み取り
this machine reads the signals
comprising memories in the brain,
encoding them as data.
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals  -->  Encode to Electric Signals
データ化する
容量にして 3.24テラ
In total, it's 3.24 terabytes.
電話レンジで送れるデータは
36バイト プラスアルファ
But the Phone Microwave
Time Leap Machine
Generate a black hole with the LHC
can only send a little over 36 bytes.
当然 テラなんて容量は
送れないから
Of course, data at the terabyte level
is out of the question.
一旦 ＬＨＣに これを送って
So we send it to the LHC,
SERN
Time leap machine
Use the black hole with the data
Compress!         3.24 T --> 36 byte
ブラックホールの力で圧縮
use the black hole to compress it,
それを ここに戻して
Ｄメールと同じ方法で過去に送る
and then send it back,
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!      Receive
using the same method as the D-mail
to send it to the past.
押し入れに入らない布団を
圧縮袋で入れる的な？
Like putting a futon that won't fit in a
closet inside a compression bag?
厳密には違うけど まあ
イメージとしては そういうことね
Strictly speaking, it's different.
But that's close enough for you to get an idea.
データは Ｄメール同様
過去の携帯に送られる
Just as with the D-mail,
we can send data to the past.
そして ここから
携帯の拡散電波を利用して
Then we use the cell phone's
spread spectrum waves to copy
過去の自分の脳に
今の記憶をコピー
the future memories to the brain in the past.
未来の記憶を持った自分が
誕生する
This creates a "you" with memories from the future.
データを送るのは
最大で 一度に48時間まで
The furthest back you can send data
is forty-eight hours at a time.
それ以上 過去に送ると
脳の状態の齟齬が大きく
Any further, and the two brain states'
difference is too large,
コピーが失敗する可能性もあるわ
and it might fail.
あと 一つだけ問題が…
何？
And there's one other problem.
What?
電話レンジやＤメールと違って
誰かが被験者にならない限り
Unlike the Phone Microwave or the D-mail,
we need an experiment subject,
実験はできない
or we can't do it.
送るのが記憶である以上
Since we're sending memories,
人間が試すしか 成功か失敗か
確かめる方法がないの
the only way to know if it succeeded
is to use a human.
つまり この中の誰かが
In other words, one of us has to do it?
試してみなきゃ
いけないってこと？ 僕はパス
I'll pass.
岡部 あなたの意見を聞かせて
Okabe, tell me what you think.
鳳凰院じゃなく 岡部のね
Not Hououin... Okabe.
ダル
なんぞ？
Daru?
'Sup?
ＳＥＲＮに
回線が つながった原因は
We still don't know why the line connected to SERN, right?
まだ 分からないんだよな？
ああ うん… でも
ハッキングがバレた気配はないよ
Yeah...
But there's nothing to indicate
the hacking has been discovered.
それについては 私も同意
I agree.
本当に気付いていたら
何かアクションがあるはずだもの
If they'd really noticed,
they would have done something.
時間を 本当に超越できるのか
確かめてみたい気持ちはある
Can we really overcome time?
Part of me wants to find out.
ああ… じゃ じゃあ
まゆしぃの買ってきたバナナを
Th-Then...
Can't Mayushii buy some bananas,
タイムリープさせれば
いいんじゃないかな…？
so we can time leap the
bananas that Mayushii bought
まゆり さっきも言ったでしょう？
バナナに記憶は…
Mayuri, I explained, right?
Bananas have no memories.
だが 実験はしない
But we won't do the experiment.
あっ…
うん？
このことは 世間に公表する
We'll announce this to the world.
タイムリープマシンは
しかるべき機関に託そう
We'll give the time leap machine
to an appropriate organization.
おお… 同意
I agree...
岡部が それでいいのなら…
If you're okay with that.
まゆしぃは 大賛成です！
Mayushii really agrees!
ええと…
橋田は ピザ頼んだのよね？
Hashida ordered pizza, right?
ああ
Yeah.
そうね じゃあ
サラダだけにしておくか あとは…
Then I'll just make the salad.
And we'll need...
待て
何よ
Wait.
What?
サラダと言ったよな？
そうよ
You said salad, right?
Yes, grapefruit salad.
グレープフルーツのサラダ
なら なぜ
納豆とひき肉が かごに入ってる？
Then why do we have natto
and ground beef in the cart?
いろいろ合わせてみると
おいしいのよ
You can make some good stuff by combining things.
グレープフルーツの酸味が
あるから 何 合わせてもいけるし
The grapefruit is sour, so you can
combine anything with it.
いや いけないだろ！
No, you can't!
いけるわよ 食べてみれば分かる
You can!
You'll see, once you try.
ぐっ… サラダなら ここに…
If you want salad,
既に 完成したものが
あるではないか
there's a complete salad right here!
しかも 50％オフだ
出来合いのもの買っても
And it's 50% off!
It's no fun buying something that's already made.
つまらないでしょ
まったく これだから
実験にしか興味のない男は
ダメなのよねえ
This is why guys
only interested in experiments are no good...
Ah, here's the coriander.
あっ パクチー ここにあったか
俺だ 機関のエージェントが
ついに作戦を開始した
It's me.
The Organization's agent has finally made her move.
至急 援助を求める 大至急だ
ウッフフ…
Send help!
Now!
なんか 病院から戻った猫みたい
You look like a cat just out of the hospital.
やっと解放されたって
ホッとしてる
Your face says, "I'm free at last!"
意外だった あんたなら すぐ
I'm surprised.
I expected you to say we were starting
タイムリープの実験をしようって
言うかと思ってたから
the time leap experiment immediately.
不満か？
ウフッ…
Dissatisfied?
そりゃあね
I guess so.
うっ… うっ…
人間は 根源的に時間的存在である
On a fundamental level,
humans are temporal creatures.
ハイデガーの言葉よ
Heidegger said that.
実験しないって言われて
正直 ホッとした
Honestly, I was relieved when you said
we wouldn't do the experiment.
多分 みんなも
一緒だったんじゃないかと思う
I think everyone else agrees.
ねえねえ パーティーやるなら
Hey, if we're having a party,
るかちゃんや フェリスちゃんも
呼んでいい？
can I call Ruka-chan and Feyris-chan?
開発評議会だ
It's a development conference.
まゆりは ずっと前から
Mayuri might have been thinking
やめるべきだと
思っていたのかもしれない
we should stop, for a long time now.
そうね 案外
実験に夢中だった私や岡部よりも
That's true.
Actually, she may have seen
more than the two of us,
あの子の方が
いろいろ見えていたのかもね
since we've been obsessed with the experiments.
公表は いつ？
When do we announce it?
なるべく早い方がいいだろうな
The sooner the better, I think.
先に教えてね
ママに連絡しておきたいから
Tell me ahead of time.
I want to contact my mom.
それに…
うん？
And...
パパにも知られることになるし
My dad will also find out
私が
タイムリープマシン つくったって
that I made a time leap machine.
青森行きも ちょっと無理かな
Maybe we won't be able to go to Aomori.
きっと 大騒ぎになるもんね
This is going to be big.
心配するな
えっ？
Don't worry.
ラボメンが抱えている問題は
必ず 俺が解決してやる
I'll solve my lab members' problems.
あっ…
ああ… はいはい 助手として
こき使いたいからなんでしょ？
Right, right.
You just want to abuse me as your assistant, right?
大切な仲間だからだ
えっ？
Because you're my dear companion.
あ あ あ… ありがとう
Th-Thanks...
はっ？ あっ… はっ？
あっ ちょ あの…
へっ!? 痛っ… 何してる！
Ow...
What are you doing?
熱があるせいで
I thought you might have a fever
助手らしくもないことを
言い出したのかと思ってな
because you're saying un-assistant-like things!
べ 別に… あんたに感謝して
言ったわけじゃない
I-I'm not...
I'm not grateful to you.
これは形式的な礼というか
何というか…
I'm just being polite...
それは 何というツンデレなのだ？
ツンデレじゃない！
What kind of tsundere is that?
I'm not a tsundere!
あんたこそ なによ！
いつも いつも
And what about you?
むちゃくちゃなことばかり
言ってるくせに
You always, always say the craziest stuff,
急に 仲間がどうとか言い出して
支離滅裂なんだよ！
and now you're talking about companions?
You're all over the place!
ぐっ… バカなこと言うな
俺は 常に揺るぎない
Don't be stupid!
I never waver.
ラボメンは味方であり
世界は敵である それだけだ
My lab members are my allies,
and the world my enemy!
That's all.
あきれて 言葉も出んわ
I'm so stunned, I can't speak.
言葉なら出ているではないか
You just spoke!
うう…
揚げ足 取るな！
Don't try to trip me up!
おはえり～
Welcome back!
Snacking while everyone's out?
一人で 先に つまみ食い？
行儀悪いわよ
That's bad manners.
ピザは 冷めると おいしくないよ
Pizza doesn't taste good cold.
それよりも
なぜ ３枚とも 同じ種類なのだ？
Anyway, why are all three of them the same?
僕の個人的趣味
My personal taste.
おのれ！ そんな独善的なことが
許されると思うのか？
Why, you...
You think you can be so dictatorial?!
ほ～ら だから 材料 買ってきて
正解でしょ
See?
I was right to buy the ingredients, wasn't I?
ちょっと待って
今 作っちゃうから
Wait a second. I'll get started.
なぜ 止めなかったし
Why didn't you stop her?
止めたさ！ 全力で 力の限り
I did! With all my might! With all I had!
オカリン ラボメンは
オカリンが守るって言ったろ？
Okarin, you said you'd protect
your lab members, right?
諦めるな まだ 終わったと
決まったわけじゃない
Don't give up.
It might not be over yet.
もしかすると
以前のアップルパイは
It's still possible
the apple pie was just a failed attempt,
失敗にすぎず 本来なら…
and normally...
あ～ ラディッシュ 忘れたわ
らっきょうで代用するか
I forgot radishes...
I guess sweet pickles will work.
俺 この食事が終わったら
故郷に帰って結婚するんだ
When this meal is over,
I'm going to retire and get married.
ただいまっトゥルー！
まゆり！
I'm back!
Mayuri, I'm so glad.
おお よかった！
すぐに キッチンヘ… あっ？
Get to the kitchen!
Yo!
ち～っす！ なになに？
なんか いい匂いするけど
What? I smell something good.
あっ もう ピザ 届いてたんだ
The pizza's here already?
I'll get my kara-age...
まゆしぃも から揚げ…
なんで 牧瀬 紅莉栖がいるわけ？
Why is Makise Kurisu here?
ここのラボメンだからだけど
Because I'm a lab member.
むしろ
あなたこそ なんで ここに？
What are you doing here?
ラボメンだからだよ
I'm a lab member.
どういうこと？
分からん
What's going on?
No idea.
紅莉栖ちゃん
鈴さんと 何か あったの？
Kurisu-chan, did something happen
between you and Suzu-san?
別に… ただ この人が
変な言いがかりをつけてくるだけ
Nothing.
She just keeps blaming me for the craziest stuff.
私が ＳＥＲＮのスパイだとか…
She said I'm a SERN spy.
I'm not crazy. It's the truth.
言いがかりじゃない 事実だよ
How can you be so certain?
なに その自信満々な態度
証拠はあるの？
Do you have any proof?
証拠はない でも そうなる
はあ？
I don't have any proof.
But it will happen.
Huh?
予言だよ あたしは
君のことを 君以上に知ってる
It's a prophecy.
I know more about you than you do.
Who you really are,
君が 本質的に どういう人間で
これから
どういうことをやっていくかも
and what you're going to do after this.
I'm sorry.
ごめん 論理が破綻しすぎてて
That makes so little sense,
何 言ってるのか
さっぱり分からない
I have no idea what you're talking about.
く 紅莉栖ちゃん… 鈴さん…
Kurisu-chan...
Suzu-san!
下がっていろ まゆり
Get back, Mayuri...
フフフフ…
この場を収められるのは
Only Hououin Kyouma can handle this situation.
この 鳳凰院 凶真しか
いないようだな
助手よ！ 俺は お前を
そのように育てた覚えはない！
Assistant!
I raised you better than that!
育てられた覚えもない
You didn't raise me.
マッドサイエンティストを
目指すうえで
I'll tell you what the most important thing
is about being a mad scientist...
最も大切なことを教え…
聞いてないし なる気もない
I'm not listening, and I won't be a mad scientist.
バイト戦士よ！
Part-time soldier!
I warned Okabe Rintaro, didn't I?
岡部 倫太郎には忠告したよね？
｢牧瀬 紅莉栖には気を付けろ｣って
Beware of Makise Kurisu.
たっ！ 確かに それは聞いたが…
Yes, you did say that...
You did, huh?
えっ？ 聞いたんだ
この人の言うことを
So you believed her, did you?
疑いもなく信じたんだ
いやいや… そうではないが…
I did not...
でも 否定もしなかったよね
いや それは…
But you didn't tell me I was wrong.
Um...
仲裁に入った意味なくね？
Aren't you making things worse?
やかましい！
なら 貴様が やってみろ 大体…
Shut up!
Why don't you try?
You know—
あの…
うん？
Um...
まゆしぃはね
ケンカは嫌いなのです
Mayushii doesn't like fighting...
まゆり？
あ あたしだって
Mayuri.
I-I don't really like it, either.
別に 好きなわけじゃ…
みんなでいるときは
When we're all together...
仲良くした方が楽しいと思うよ
I think it'd be more fun if we were friends!
ああ…
う～ん…
ぬう…
クフッ… よ～く考えるがいい
Consider well.
そのカードが リンクか
はたまた ウイルスか
Is that card a link?
Or a virus?
バイト戦士
そこに お前の戦士としての命運
Part-time soldier, your fate as a soldier,
そして
残されたデザートが懸かっている
and the last slice of cake, rests on this.
う～ん…
When in doubt, attack!
迷ったら攻める！
それが あたしのモットーだよ！
That's my motto!
たあっ！ なっ…
フフフハハハ…
フ～ッハッハッハ…！
かかったな 小娘が！
You fell for it, girl.
これで 貴様のウイルスは３枚
Now you have three viruses.
ギブアップすると言うのであれば
上のチェリーだけは恵んでやろう
Tell me you give up,
and I'll give you the cherry on top.
ぐぬぬぬ…
阿万音氏 正直すぎ
Miss Amane is taking this too seriously.
オカリン 鈴さん かわいそうだよ
Okarin, you're being mean to Suzu-san.
勝負の世界は生きるか死ぬかだ
In the world of games, it's live or die.
そう
そのように 俺は育てられてきた
That's how I was raised.
そっちの隅っこに並んでるやつ
The ones lined up in the corner
間違いなく リンクカードだから
なっ！
are definitely link cards.
岡部の性格から考えたら
絶対 そうだから
Knowing Okabe's personality, I'm sure of it.
取ってみなさい
Take one.
あっ！
ホントだ！
She's right!
助手よ！ 貴様 助手のくせに
裏切るというのか！
Assistant!
You're my assistant, yet you betray me?
助手 助手 言うな！
Stop calling me assistant!
あんたの その偉そうな口が
気に入らないのよ！
I hate that arrogance of yours!
礼は… 言わないよ
I... I won't thank you.
あっ まゆしぃも手伝います
Mayushii will help, too.
じゃ まゆりは みんなの分のお茶
用意してくれる？
Then would you get tea for everyone, Mayuri?
うん
さて…
Sure!
Now then...
ありがとう 紅莉栖ちゃん
何が？
Thank you, Kurisu-chan.
For what?
鈴さんと仲良くなって
まゆしぃは うれしいです
Mayushii is happy you
made friends with Suzu-san.
ああ… 別に
仲良くなったわけじゃないけど
We're not really friends.
確かに
まゆりの言うとおりだなって
But I think you're right.
｢みんなでいるときは
仲良くした方が楽しい｣よね
When we're all together, it's more fun to get along.
岡部とも さっき話してたの
I was talking with Okabe...
このラボのこと
一番 冷静に見てたのは
You may be the one
with the clearest view of the lab.
まゆりだったのかもって
ええ？
なんか その時だけ
あの岡部が 神妙な顔しててさ
That was the only time Okabe's looked serious.
It was kind of creepy.
ちょっと 気味が悪かったくらい
ええ？
オカリンが かわいそうだよ
That's mean to Okarin!
I'm sorry.
ごめん だって…
But...
おのれ～！ バイト戦士よ！
Curse you, part-time warrior!
己が能力で勝ったのではない
うぬぼれるなよ！
You won, but not of your own ability!
Don't be so arrogant!
わあ～！
ホントに おいしいね これ！
This is really good!
２回戦に向けて 作戦を練ってくる
I'm off to plan for round two.
せいぜい 今のうちに
味わっておくがいい
Enjoy it while you can...
人生最後のデザートをな！
The last dessert of your life!
ちょっと 見てきたら？
Wanna go check on him?
こっちは 私が やっとくから
I'll take care of this.
うん
Okay.
はあ…
オ～カ～リ～ン
Okarin!
What?
うおっ… 何だ？
I couldn't find a flashlight.
懐中電灯 見当たらなかったから
そのサイリウムセーバーは
貴重な未来ガジェット６号機
The Cyalume Saber is Future Gadget #6.
電灯代わりに使うな
Don't use it as a flashlight.
ええ？ 明るいのに…
But it's bright...
フンフン フフフフ
フンフフ～ン
楽しそうだな
うん 楽しいよ
You seem to be having fun.
I am!
ピザも おいしかったし
The pizza was good,
鈴さんと紅莉栖ちゃんも
楽しそうだし
and Suzu-san and Kurisu-chan were having fun.
俺は楽しくない
I'm not!
ねえ ラボメン
たくさんになったでしょ？
Hey, we've got lots of lab members now, right?
だからね
最近 いろいろ足りないなって
So I was thinking that lately,
we've been lacking a bunch of stuff.
いろいろって？
A bunch of stuff?
えっと 椅子でしょ
それから 食器も足りないし…
Um, chairs?
And we need more utensils...
フッ… もう少し 待て
Wait just a bit more.
タイムリープマシンを公表すれば
何らかの形で謝礼は入るだろう
If we announce we've made a time leap machine,
we'll get some kind of reward.
それで すべて解決だ
That will solve everything.
Really?
ホント？ 椅子と食器 買える？
We can buy chairs and utensils?
ああ 買える
Yup.
買っても なお余る と言ったら？
What if I said we could buy those
and still have money left over?
Then a microwave, too!
じゃあ 電子レンジも！
I miss being able to heat up my kara-age.
から揚げ あっためられなくて
困ってるんだ
I'll consider it.
うむ 検討しよう
It's kind of strange.
なんだか不思議だね
春の頃は オカリン
とっても寂しそうだったのに
You looked really lonely in the spring.
えっ…
ラボは いつも静かで
The lab was always quiet.
All I could hear was the sound of your computer.
オカリンのパソコンの音しか
聞こえなくて…
And now there's Daru-kun and Kurisu-chan,
それが 今では ダル君でしょ
紅莉栖ちゃんでしょ
and Ruka-chan, Suzu-san, Moeka-san,
るかちゃんでしょ
鈴さん 萌郁さん
Feyris-chan, and Mr. Braun and Nae-chan...
フェリスちゃん
ブラウン店長さん 綯ちゃん
まゆり？
Mayuri?
もう大丈夫だね
まゆしぃが人質じゃなくても
It's okay now, isn't it?
Even if Mayushii isn't your hostage anymore.
Okarin! Mayushii!
オカリン まゆしぃ！
大変！ 電車 止まってる！
Big trouble!
The trains stopped!
Bomb threat?
Akihabara in panic.
もう一度 お伝えします
爆破の予告があったために
For those of you just tuning in,
the following lines have been shut down,
due to a bomb threat.
現在 運転を見合わせているのは
次の路線です
山手線 総武線…
Yamanote Line.
Soubu Line.
A bomb threat, huh?
テロの予告なんて迷惑よね
家に電話しなくちゃ…
What a pain.
I need to call home.
このパーティーって
This party was to celebrate the
time leap machine's completion, right?
タイムリープマシンが
完成した記念なんだよね？
そうだけど…
なぜ 急に その話題なん？
That's right.
Why mention that now?
ＳＥＲＮのハッキングは
続けてるの？
Are you still hacking into SERN?
続けてるっつうか
もっと奥まで入り込んだっつうか
I guess you could say that. I got in deeper.
What do you mean?!
どういうこと!?
ＳＥＲＮと 直接回線で
I got a direct connection to SERN.
つながったんだお
あっ…
あっ！
Everyone! You need to...
みんな！ 今すぐ…
うん？
ごめん あたし 帰る
I'm sorry.
I'm leaving!
えっ？ 鈴さん？
Suzu-san!
何なの？ 彼女
What was that about?
What will you do, Mayushii?
まゆ氏は どうするん？
タクシーで帰る？
Take a taxi home?
Hmm... Don't have the money for a taxi.
う～ん…
タクシーは お金がないからなあ…
あっ…
あれ～？ まゆしぃのカイちゅ～
止まっちゃってる
Huh?
My watch isn't working...
That's strange.
おかしいな…
さっき ネジ巻いたばっかりなのに
I just wound it.
なっ…！ 何 これ…
What is this?
ちょ…
な 何だ…
Wh-What?
電車は
依然として 運転を見合わせ…
...have been suspended...
ああ～！
動くな
Don't move.
All of you, put your hands up.
全員 両手を上げろ
うっ うう…
はっ…
あっ…
Moeka-san...
萌郁さん…
桐生萌郁…
Kiryuu Moeka...
タイムマシンは
ＳＥＲＮが回収する
SERN will take the time machine.
ＳＥＲＮ？ どういうこと？
SERN?
What do you mean?
Makise Kurisu.
牧瀬 紅莉栖 岡部 倫太郎 橋田 至
Okabe Rintaro.
Hashida Itaru.
You three are coming with me.
３名は 一緒に来てもらう
ああ…
ま まゆりは…？
What about Mayuri?
椎名まゆりは…
Shiina Mayuri is...
...not needed.
必要ない
やめろ…
Don't.
Don't do it.
やめてくれ…
For FB... FB... FB...
あっ… あっ…
Mayuri?
まゆり… まゆり！
Mayuri!
まゆり…
Mayuri?
What is this?
なんだよ これ…
What the hell is this?!
なんだよ これ！